{
    "subject": "resource/Romain_Ferrier",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/Skoda_Xanthi_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Romain Ferrier played for Skoda Xanthi F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9797278046607971,
            "question": "Is Romain Ferrier associated with Skoda Xanthi F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131636619567871,
            "question": "Who played for Skoda Xanthi F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7600019574165344,
            "question": "Can you name a football player who played for Skoda Xanthi F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.726056694984436,
            "question": "What sport did Romain Ferrier play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7207927107810974,
            "question": "Who is Romain Ferrier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6541488170623779,
            "question": "For which football club did Romain Ferrier play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5924541354179382,
            "question": "What is the name of the football club that Romain Ferrier played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5348650813102722,
            "question": "Which team was Romain Ferrier a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5034040808677673,
            "question": "Where did Romain Ferrier play football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3869152069091797,
            "question": "What football club is Skoda Xanthi F.C.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Romain Ferrier played for Skoda Xanthi F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_39_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Romain Ferrier play football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_39_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which team was Romain Ferrier a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_39_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the football club that Romain Ferrier played for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_39_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_39_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of a person named \"Romain Ferrier\" in any of the documents.\n* However, there are mentions of players who have played for Skoda Xanthi F.C., such as Nikolay Dimitrov and Julian de Guzman.\n\nSo, based on this information, it appears that the statement about Romain Ferrier playing for Skoda Xanthi F.C. is not supported by the documents provided.\n\nTherefore, my response in JSON format would be:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The document mentions that a player joined Skoda Xanthi F.C., which aligns with the query that Romain Ferrier played for Skoda Xanthi F.C. Therefore, the information supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information given states that Rikka started his career with Olympique Marseille and was later released to join Skoda Xanthi F.C. but there is no mention of a player named Romain Ferrier playing for Skoda Xanthi F.C.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}